(Leonard:)It seems like something
we should talk about.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Penny:)Well, would you consider
mounds of credit card debt
(Leonard:)kind of a big deal
financially?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Penny:)Huh.
(Howard:)Mm. So, me and the guys
were talking about
(Howard:)this great
investment opportunity...
(Bernadette:)Nope.
(Howard:)But you didn't hear what it was.
(Howard:)I know.
(Howard:)Oh, come on.
(Bernadette:)Fine. What is it?
(Howard:)It's to help reopen
the comic book store.
(Bernadette:)Nope.
(Howard:)Well, hear me out.
(Bernadette:)Howard, you know
we're saving up for a house.
(Howard:)I know, but all the guys
are doing it.
(Howard:)We're splitting it four ways, so
it's really not that much money.
(sighs) It just seems
like a risky investment.
(Howard:)I get that. I...
(sighs)
(chuckles):
Okay, look...
(sighs)
The reason this is important
is... (clears throat)